[
    {"question":"5+5 = ?","ans1":"10","ans2":"11","ans3":"12","ans4":"13","correctAns":"10"},
    {"question":"5-4 = ?","ans1":"0","ans2":"15","ans3":"1","ans4":"14","correctAns":"1"},
    {"question":"What does a cat say?","ans1":"woof","ans2":"meow","ans3":"ribbet","ans4":"moo","correctAns":"meow"},
    {"question":"34+5 = ?","ans1":"66","ans2":"39","ans3":"33","ans4":"13","correctAns":"39"},
    {"question":"The first 3 digits of pi are what?","ans1":"3.14","ans2":"3.13","ans3":"3.12","ans4":"3.00","correctAns":"3.14"},
    {"question":"6 * 5 = ?","ans1":"3.14","ans2":"3","ans3":"30","ans4":"-3","correctAns":"30"},
    {"question":"6 * 4 = ?","ans1":"3.14","ans2":"3","ans3":"24","ans4":"-3","correctAns":"24"},
    {"question":"6 * 3 = ?","ans1":"1","ans2":"3","ans3":"18","ans4":"-3","correctAns":"18"},
    {"question":"6 * 2 = ?","ans1":"14","ans2":"12","ans3":"30","ans4":"-55","correctAns":"12"},
    {"question":"6 * 0 = ?","ans1":"3","ans2":"2","ans3":"0","ans4":"-3","correctAns":"0"}

]